So spacious.
Cool.
So cool.
Do we have to be like that too?
You go.
Hello, everyone.
I'm the martial arts instructor of Incomplete Summer training camp.
My name is Yang Jian.
Hello.
Hello, Mr.Yang.
Well then.
I'd like to get to know everyone a bit.
Starting with you.
My name is Zhang Ziyu.
As for martial arts,
I really haven't practiced before.
But I have practiced some dance.
I can do a split.
Could you show us?
Show us.
Actually, he's pretty good at this.
Of course he is.
Very good.
A flexible man.
And I can also do a cartwheel.
Let me try.
OK, show us.
Be careful.
Stay safe.
Careful.
It's too slippery.
We've already known Zhang Ziyu's amazing abilities.
Thank you, sir.
Very impressive.
Next one.
I haven't learned martial arts either.
But I can do some
pretty basic moves,
like a kip-up and a cartwheel.
Come on, show us.
Show us.
Come on.
Good.
Now a cartwheel.
This one's good.
Impressive.
Your turn.
I've never learned martial arts.
And I can't do a cartwheel, a kip-up,
or the splits either.
That's okay.
We're here to learn today.
Good, keep it up.
Thank you, sir.
Keep it up.
Your turn.
Hello, Mr.Yang. My name is Bai Guanyu.
I'm also a complete beginner.
I'll work hard to keep up with everyone,
and not hold anyone back.
Hello, Mr.Yang. I'm Ma Weixian.
I practiced taekwondo as a kid.
I was a black belt in elementary school.
I can do some flying kicks,
high blocks, middle blocks,
and some poomsae, or forms.
I studied taekwondo for many years.
Let me do a flying kick.
Okay.
Like this.
This is a flying kick in Taekwondo.
I can also do a handstand, Mr.Yang.
Hold my feet for a second.
Good, very good.
Go all out.
I really love martial arts.
Very good.
Hello, Mr.Yang. I'm Jiang Xiaomeng.
Back in college,
I learned a little martial arts stuff,
like sword flourishes and spear twirling.
As for the kip-up,
I think I can pull it off.
Give it a try.
One more challenge, a kip-up.
Encourage him.
Keep it up.
Go.
Good, very good.
Hello, Mr.Yang. My name is Zhou Guorui.
And honestly,
I don't know anything.
I'm just here to learn as much as I can.
Okay.
We're about to do a live sparring session.
It'll be you guys against
my four assistant coaches.
What?
We fight them?
We'd get beaten to a pulp.
We're gonna die right here and now.
Sir, I can only kneel and beg for mercy.
In pairs, act out a martial arts fight.
The plot is as follows.
Two people come here to rescue someone,
and fight four opponents,
When they finally find the person,
they realize they're too late.
Each pair needs to come up with
and flesh out their own fight scene,
including the setting,
character relationships,
who they're rescuing,
dialogue, and the performance.
Stay true to the story at all times.
No breaking character.
Ma Weixian.
Let's discuss the plot.
Since they ask 'Who goes there, '
I think we should make it more vintage.
How about a swordsman?
Here
I think we can make it a bit more comedic.
Comedy is more fun.
I'm the Prince.
And you're my guard.
I'm the prince. I'm playing yesterday's role.
You really don't look like a Prince.
And you're such a tall Prince,
why would you have a skinny guard like me?
That can't be right.
Fine.
I'll give you a villain to play.
So you can act your heart out.
Okay.
I guess I'll just play this prince.
You're a preener.
Prince.
Preener.
Then maybe our characters should
have different personalities.
Right.
Personalities.
My character might be a bit more fierce and determined.
Right, fierce and determined.
Then my character's the sunny one.
Right.
Angry.
Honestly, being our true selves is enough.
Our true selves.
I might add a sentence here.
Guorui, I don't know why,
but my power is especially strong today.
Did you get bitten?
I don't know.
I wasn't.
Let's hurry and save Mingyang.
Let's go find Mingyang.
Mingyang can save me.
Let's go.
Okay.
No problem.
First group, come forward.
We.
It's now the year 5070 AD.
The Zombie Virus broke out,
and the only people left on Earth
are me, Guorui, and Mingyang.
And Mingyang too.
Once when I went out,
I was unfortunately bitten by a zombie.
Only Mingyang's serum can save me.
Because Sun Mingyang is
a Super Serum Immune.
But this news was found out by the Experiment Department.
They took Mingyang away.
But only Mingyang's serum
can save me.
So Guorui and I
are now going to the Experiment Department
to rescue Mingyang.
Yes.
Rescue Ziyu.
Save me.
Three, two, one, go.
Who goes there?
Take a guess.
What business do you have here?
Here to rescue
Sun Mingyang.
No more talk. Let's go.
Guorui.
I feel like my strength today is abnormally powerful.
What's wrong?
I don't know why.
But I feel like all the blood in my body is about to burst out.
Then let's hurry
and find them.
Beat the fallen one?
There must be some traps here.
Let's be careful,
so we don't get ambushed.
Sun Mingyang.
Quick, open it.
My hands are shaking a little.
What is this?
Mingyang?
How did you become a pot of grass?
That's a cactus.
Is this Mingyang?
It even has a mouth.
Is it really Mingyang?
Can it bite you?
Wait, this one
really does look like him.
Sun Mingyang.
Sun Mingyang, get up, time for makeup.
I'll draw your inner eyeliner, Sun Mingyang.
Come out quick, Sun Mingyang.
Sun Mingyang.
What do we do without you?
I'll draw your inner eyeliner.
What do we do?
We're done for, Guorui.
Why won't my hand obey me?
Hurry, let's go.
I'm feeling a bit unwell.
Got any herbal stuff?
Let me have a sip.
I'm feeling a bit unwell.
Sun Mingyang.
We've come to save you.
Help!
Cut.
Good.
Not bad.
For this set of moves,
the two of you worked well together.
Going forward, you still need more work
on straight punches, striking, and coordination.
Okay.
Not bad.
Come on.
Thank you.
Back in line.
Second team.
Thank you, Mr.Yang.
I am a prince who has traveled the world.
My greatest hobby is
saving princesses.
Save one, love one.
Fall for one, dump one.
This is my sword-bearing guard.
The princess we're rescuing this time
is a princess this guard
has long been in love with.
And I promised him
after this job, we're out for good.
Three, two, one, action.
Who goes there?
None of your business.
Sir,
we're here to save the princess.
Who told you to say that?
Enough talk, attack.
Can you handle it?
Useless, so slow.
I have to do it myself.
What did I hire you for?
Go find the princess.
What's this?
Could it be the clues the Princess left?
It seems the princess is in this box.
How is that possible?
You open it.
A rice bowl.
Princess.
Prin...
Look, couldn't hold it in, could you?
It's useless now.
If you like it, keep it and eat it.
I'm off to find the next Princess.
Are you coming or not? Hurry up.
Princess.
It.
There are so many Princesses in the world.
What does it matter if this one is gone?
Come with me, hurry up.
Go.
Hurry up.
If you won't leave, I will.
Do you even have a heart?
The Princess was so good to you.
Now she's become like this,
and you're just going to leave.
There's more than one who's good to me.
There are plenty of Princesses.
I ain't serving you anymore.
You love this Princess.
You love her.
Why don't you look in the mirror?
You're just a guard,
and you want to marry a princess?
Princess.
I say, just spend your life with that bowl of noodles.
If you won't do it, I'll find another.
Prince.
The Princess left a letter over there.
A letter?
Is there any money in it?
Let me see.
Did she write my name in her will?
Where is it?
Here it is.
A heartless man like you
doesn't deserve to live.
To the outside world,
I'll tell them
you died for your princess and country.
But here,
no one knows how you died.
It's okay.
Out there, I'll leave you a good name.
Princess.
I'm coming for you.
Okay, cut.
Princess.
I missed you.
I'm taking you home right now.
We're taking you home together.
Snail rice noodles.
What's this?
Smells so good.
Very good.
Much better than I expected.
But I hope from now on,
you'll still focus more on basic training.
Okay, got it.
Come on.
We'll work hard.
Group three, get ready.
Ruijian and I love the same person.
Our loved one was kidnapped by the gang.
Now we're going to defeat the gang
and rescue our loved one.
In the end, the one we both loved was already barely alive,
and I still...
Alright, no more talking.
Okay, stop here.
Stay tuned.
But the loved one we rescued is named
Mingyang.
Yes, Mingyang is the one we both love.
Mingyang again?
Mingyang again.
Bound to a Everyone Loves Me System.
Come on.
Let's go.
My love, come to me.
What do I do?
It's just this troublesome.
Everyone loves me.
Three, two, one, action.
Who goes there?
Ma Weixian, who loves Mingyang.
Wang Ruijian, ready for Mingyang.
What's your business?
Looking for my other half.
No more talk. Attack.
Don't.
Mingyang.
How dare they touch it?
-How did you become a frog? -Mingyang.
He's still alive.
Sun
What?
Mingyang.
Mingyang, what's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Mingyang.
How did you turn into a frog?
Mingyang, what's wrong?
This is all your fault.
Save him, hurry.
Mingyang.
Hurry, do artificial respiration.
I'll do it.
You do it.
Mingyang.
No way.
Mingyang is dying.
Mingyang.
Ruijian, just kiss it.
He actually kissed it.
Give it to me.
Mingyang, I'm sorry.
Mingyang.
I can't do it.
Don't run, Mingyang.
Mingyang.
This is all your fault.
Why?
Mingyang.
It's all because of you.
That Mingyang was captured.
Now he's turned into a frog.
Mingyang.
Mingyang, I'm so sorry.
No!
Mingyang.
It's all your fault.
I'm so sorry.
If you'd been a bit faster,
this wouldn't have happened.
Mingyang.
Why?
It's about to collapse.
It's collapsing, let's go.
I'm not leaving.
Go!
Hurry, go!
I'm not leaving.
Take Mingyang with us.
Hurry up and go!
I'm not leaving.
It's about to collapse.
I want to die here with Mingyang.
Go!
Save me.
What's that?
There really is a frog.
It really is a frog.
So gross.
They actually dare to touch it.
Your moves just now had a bit
too much brute force.
Too much brute force.
You can easily get hurt when you fall.
Never land on your elbow first in the future.
Right.
Although it looked very real,
be sure to stay safe.
Okay.
Alright?
Okay, Group Four.
Come on, listen to the story.
We drew inspiration from a novel.
We paid tribute to a novel called
Strange Tales from a Chinese Studio.
So, our story is set in ancient times.
I'm the Bai family's eldest young master.
I am the Bai family's second young master.
Then our purpose in coming here
to save our mother.
Three, two, one, action.
Who goes there?
Eldest Young Master Bai.
Second Young Master Bai.
Who introduce themselves like that?
What business do you have?
Rescuing our mother.
Enough talk, attack.
Brother, we gotta go.
Turned into an urn?
Zhixuan, look what this is.
Zhixuan must be trying not to laugh.
I feel like...
What's this?
Is this really our mother?
Zhixuan.
Do you remember?
Dad said something before he died:
Mother was transformed from a tree branch.
Mother,
how did you become
a foot soaking basin?
Mother.
We're taking you home.
Actually,
Second Young Master Bai is long dead.
Chen family, your enemy.
My mother has three lives,
and she gave me her second one.
You?
You think you can wipe out my Bai family?
But you forgot
your Bai family
still has a secret treasure in my hands.
Are they filming a short drama?
Plot twist after plot twist.
What is that thing?
It's still in my hand.
Which proves the Bai family's fate
is also in my hand.
I asked you what it is.
You know exactly what it is.
How could you throw your mom like that?
Give it back to me.
Take one more step
and I'll crush it.
No.
What do you want?
Tell me.
I want everyone in the Bai family
to die.
Fine, I promise you.
Come on!
What is this? Self-destruction?
Is he grabbing waist flags over there?
Good, cut.
Totally improvised.
Actually, for the rest of it, we didn't prepare much, sir.
Everyone's performance this time
exceeded my expectations.
I didn't expect you to memorize
the moves so quickly.
And knock all four of my assistants
to the ground.
You really can stand the test.
Our training has only just begun.
High-five. Good.
High-five, sorry.
Right.
You two were pretty intense.
High-five, good.
You're too fat.
Good.
Alright, lost.
It's fine.
Too high.
Didn't hit it.
One hit.
Draw your sword.
Is this your best move?
Let him do the highest one.
He's got guts.
Draw the blade.
Draw.
Ready.
Legs straight.
One, two, three, strike.
Strike.
That felt great.
Come on, release.
Come on, Chen Zhixuan, one more slash.
Can't cut it at all.
Students,
today we tested upper-body strength and lower-body strength.
We went through fight choreography.
We went through wire work.
I hope you'll keep training hard
in the days ahead.
Keep it up.
That's all for today's training.
Class dismissed.
Thank you, Mr.Yang.
Thanks for your hard work, Mr.Yang.
Thanks for all your hard work.